<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ciprian Turcu&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>https://ciprianturcu.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ciprian Turcu&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 06:21:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ciprianturcu.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving Blogging</title>
      <link>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/moving-bloging.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 06:21:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/moving-bloging.html</guid>
      <description>Hello, Since last time, I decided to move my blogging direction to some place else. I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on something since September 2018 and It&amp;rsquo;s up, functional, at https://doxti.com. Doxti is basically a UI for http://goHugo.io , a CMS if you wish. A way to write blog posts and build them using hugo( fast, and with a specific static site builder). The catch is that you have to create them and manage them on doxti.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doxti, github, finally functional</title>
      <link>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/doxti-github-finally-functional.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 23:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/doxti-github-finally-functional.html</guid>
      <description>What did I just do? I am writing this from doxti, a local dev install, and I am proud to say, it&amp;rsquo;s publishing on github on it&amp;rsquo;s own. I&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for this moment, where I have such a tool. built by me, for years! Might not be a big thing, but with my full time job + life in the way, I never really got around to building this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doxti, hugo and a personal project</title>
      <link>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/doxti-hugo-and-a-personal-project.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 23:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/doxti-hugo-and-a-personal-project.html</guid>
      <description>A static site generator, Doxti and a personal project.A static site generator, doxti and a personal project. Are you getting it? these are not 3 separate things. This is one thing. For the record, this is officially the first post I am writing in Doxti , and will generate with doxti to publish to my site manually after.
Yes, I am using my own product to write this post. Cool heh?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuring and using aws-cli</title>
      <link>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/configuring-and-using-aws-cli.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2015 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/configuring-and-using-aws-cli.html</guid>
      <description>Configuring Run
aws configure  This will ask you for the following keys:
AWS Access Key ID [None]: AWS Secret Access Key [None]: Default region name [None]: Default output format [None]:  Create a new Access key and Secret Access key by going here https://console.aws.amazon.com/iam/home?#security_credential and selecting Access Keys, create new access key and use those credentials.
You have these regions and points:
US East (N. Virginia) -	us-east-1 US West (Oregon) - us-west-2 EU (Ireland)	eu-west-1  More you can find here: http://docs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful Git commands</title>
      <link>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/useful-git-commands.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 21:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/useful-git-commands.html</guid>
      <description>Initialize git in a working directory So you have a directory where you want to set up git in. You cd into that directory and you do
git init  That&amp;rsquo;s all it takes to have git initialized in that directory.
Connect to a remote repository Now what you want is to connect that git instance to a remote branch. To do this run:
git remote add origin &amp;lt;URL&amp;gt;  Now you&amp;rsquo;re connected to a remote repo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using huGO</title>
      <link>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/using-hugo.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 21:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/using-hugo.html</guid>
      <description>###Creating a site
All you need to create a site is to go in the folder you want to create your site and write:
hugo new site site-name  instead of &amp;ldquo;site-name&amp;rdquo; you can use &amp;ldquo;/path/to/site&amp;rdquo;. The site name is going to be a directory. When ever you want to run HuGO commands for that site you need to be in the site root folder.
###Configuring a bit
Once you ran the above command, all the site files will be generated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing and using s3cmd</title>
      <link>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/installing-and-using-s3cmd.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/installing-and-using-s3cmd.html</guid>
      <description>Download Go to http://sourceforge.net/projects/s3tools/files/s3cmd/ , select the latest version folder and download the tar.gz file. Unzip it with
tar -zxvf &amp;lt;filename&amp;gt;  Install First make sure you have python setup tools installed. To install run:
sudo apt-get install python-setuptools  Then go inside your unpacked previously directory and run:
sudo python setup.py install  And that&amp;rsquo;s it for installing. Now configuring and using:
Configuring To configure, run:
s3cmd --configure   You will be prompted for Access key and Secret Key.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Amazon S3 AWS-cli</title>
      <link>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/install-amazon-s3-aws-cli.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 19:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/install-amazon-s3-aws-cli.html</guid>
      <description>What is AWS-cli? AWS-CLI is a comand line tool that helps you manage your bucket from a command line. That&amp;rsquo;s right! once configured you can push and delete your files from your S# bucket via command line.
How do I install it? Since this is built in python,weel, first you have to have python installed. To check that and see it&amp;rsquo;s version
python --version  Then Download the installer:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install HuGO</title>
      <link>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/install-hugo.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 01:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/install-hugo.html</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s ironic is that I&amp;rsquo;m creating this page for Hugo to process and generate later. Here&amp;rsquo;s how you install (in Ubuntu) Hugo.
Jump to step 3 if you&amp;rsquo;re doing this from the terminal. 1. Go to :
https://gohugo.io/  Click &amp;ldquo;Install&amp;rdquo; and after it scrolls down click download. 2. Scroll down and select:
hugo_0.14_linux_amd64.tar.gz  Or whatever version is *_linux_amd64.tar.gz 3. To get this from the terminal: You can either:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing go,golang on Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/installing-gogolang-on-ubuntu.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2015 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/installing-gogolang-on-ubuntu.html</guid>
      <description>Installing go can be done multiple ways. After installing it via apt-get and trying to install the binary from github, I gave up, downloaded the source and did a much faster and easier install.After a long trial and error and trying to understand why everything I do works and doesn&amp;rsquo;t, I got to a place where I Do these steps exactly and you should be fine.
Here&amp;rsquo;s how I did it: I went to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello dog!</title>
      <link>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/hello-dog.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2015 22:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ciprianturcu.com/posts/hello-dog.html</guid>
      <description>What? Hello Dog is the new Hello World. This is my blog and this is obviously the first post. I am GOing to try and document some stuff here, mostly technical, about my findings, things that I try not to forget. Ever.
Hi there! Welcome to my blog. This is a totally new direction that I am trying to GO in with my website and I&amp;rsquo;m trying out something new.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>